<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Christopher Swayne</title>
    <link>https://christopherswayne.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Christopher Swayne</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>All rights reserved - 2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 23:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://christopherswayne.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Changing Themes</title>
      <link>https://christopherswayne.com/changing_themes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 23:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://christopherswayne.com/changing_themes/</guid>
      <description>Sorry for it over a month, and while I’ve been busy, my perfectionist attitude with my website has made me again and again recreate the site to my specific desires for a pleasing, and simple blog.
Now, that I’ve finally been able to complete my work of changing the theme, and figuring out after a few painstaking days of how to create, add, and display my posts, the shared trip of my life, knowledge, and experiences can be shared amongst you wonderful readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://christopherswayne.com/hello_world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 23:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://christopherswayne.com/hello_world/</guid>
      <description>Well, for a Hello World! post, this seems pretty boring. However, I’m much more pleased with this than my previous attempt to use Jekyll for local hosting to test, and build my site. Hugo has been a much easier start, and has a simpler methodology to building the site. While I’m not an expert by any means in HTML, or CSS, this attractive base theme certainly has its uses in making a good foundation for me to modify and create something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://christopherswayne.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://christopherswayne.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m a Computer Science student that attends the University of Missouri - Kansas City, in Kansas City, Missouri. I like to spend my time reading, working on projects, or tinkering with my electronics, and vehicle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Resume</title>
      <link>https://christopherswayne.com/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://christopherswayne.com/resume/</guid>
      <description>GOALS Acquire experience in a challenging and interesting environment, with a focus on learning new technologies and skills.
SKILLS &amp;amp; ABILITIES • C++ • C# • Java • Python •
Maintain and Troubleshoot OS X, Linux, and Windows Assembled numerous home systems.
EXPERIENCE Park Hill School District: November 2018 – Present Technology Support Assistant for Lakeview Middle School, and District Office • Maintain fleet of One-to-One devices for Students and Faculty.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>